Cristopher Thomas LP #27 Abercomby Street, Tel: 737-8457 St Joseph Email: Kristopherthomas673@gmail.com

Dear Sir/Madam,

Customer-centred, providing exemplary customer service leads to goal attainment. You need individuals who are able to contribute to the attainment of your companies goals, I am such an individual and as such I wish to apply for the position with in your company.

I am a self motivated, well spoken, confident and personable with considerable experience in providing excellent customer service. My work experience in the hotel industry extends over five years and during this time I have gained vast experience in hotel management, clerical skills and customer service relations. I believe I will be an asset and contribute immensely towards customer service at your organization. If afforded this opportunity my wealth of people skills will be allowed to shine.

I have attached my resume for your perusal, I am available for immediate placement and look forward to an interview at your convenience. I will follow up to discuss the opportunities with your company, I look forward to hearing from you.

Kristopher Thomas

Sincerely,

Kristopher Thomas

01/1/2015

LP #27 Abercomby Street,

Tel: 737-8457

St Joseph

Email: Kristopherthomas673@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:

To obtain a position where I can contribute as a team-player in a people-oriented organization, using my skills and experience to achieve company goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Holiday Inn Express & Suites Hotel - Front Desk Agent

June 2011 - presently

- Ensuring guest accomodations are ready
- Assit guests in locationg activites within close proximity to the hotel
- Conduct transactions pertaining to aquisition of rooms by guests
- Arrange wake up calls
- Assist guests with problems or concerns

Crowne Plaza Trinidad - Reservation Clerk/ Night Auditor April 2008 - June 2011

- Update all guest arrivals and departures
- Responsible for making and confirming reservations either by fax, email or telephone

West Palm Hotel - Reservation Clerk

July 2007 - October 2007

- Update all guest arrivals and departures
- Making and confirming reservations either by fax, email or telephone

•	Producing folio for arrivals of guests, post all bills charges from restaurant, bar, housekeeping,
	telephone, faxes or internet used by guest on a daily basics

Rich Care industries Ltd/ Cell Master (Digicel)

Customer Service Representative

March 2006 - July 2007

- Performing routine clerical functions: typing, faxing and copying

 Follow-up/ assist with order entry processing
- Assist in Cashier's desk when needed.

Inventory Clerk

Receiving, storing, distributing and marinating a proper stock level at all time.

Warehouse Assistant

May 2005 - March 2006 •

Assisting sales with their request for goods and services to and from the warehouse

- Assisting in stock taking Customer Service Representative:
- Prepare invoices, Cash invoices and Receipts

SKILLS:

■ Team player ■ Integrity & trust

■ Flexible ■ Ability to work under pressure

■ Customer focused ■ Dependable

EDUCATION:

School of International Travel and Language

2003-2004

Barataria Senior Secondary Comprehensive School

2002-2003

CXC O'Levels (General Proficiency)

- English A
- Mathematics
- Social Studies
- Woodwork
- Technical Drawing

REFERENCES:

• Mr. Randy Persad

General Manager of Taurus Concepts

#49 Southern Maid Road

Curepe

333-0505 / 729-8785

Mr. Richard Smith

General Manager

Rich Care Industries Ltd/Cell Master

(Digicel)

Fernandez Industrial Center

Eastern Main Road

Laventile

626-5324

Mrs. Adanna Graham

Front Desk Manager

Holiday Inn Express Hotel and Suites

1 Expostion Drive , Trincity

716-6941